# **JOEY VALLES**

### NETWORK ADMINISTRATOR

## Career Objective

Adaptable professional with 19.5+ years of experience and a proven knowledge of back office operations, customer service, and executive support. Aiming to leverage my skills to successfully fill the Network Administrator role at your company.

## Contact

- ioeyvalles@gmail.com
- **4** (424) 359-9332
- 45 Maleena Mesa Street Henderson , Nevada, 89074

# Education

#### I.T.T. TECHNICAL INSTITUTE

Henderson, NV Network Administration Information Technology (Aug 2001)

## Certifications

A+ Certified CNA

# Experience

#### Mar 2009 - Present

#### I.T. ADMINISTRATOR

QUICKLVPC, Las Vegas, NV

- Balance multiple schedules and installs across the valley
- Continue network maintenance and proper upgrades for future compatibility
- Create and implement security standards and practices to protect networks
- Create paperless workplaces, look for cost savings in the network infrastructures and implement them

#### Sep 2007 - Jul 2009

#### I.T. ADMINISTRATOR

AGC, Las Vegas, NV

- Run entire companies I.T. infrastructure from upgrading the network to dealing with day-to-day issues
- Administer new policies, procedures, and forecast future needs
- Stay in direct contact with the director of operations, owner, and office manager to see projects through on time and within budget
- Design and install all cable and network infrastructure for new buildings or new office build outs

## Jan 2004 - Sep 2007

#### I.T. TECHNICIAN

LVIT, Las Vegas, NV

- Answer various computer related calls, set appointments, and arrive for service or repair
- Focus on customer's long-term needs and produce affordable I.T.

strategies

- Integrate solutions for existing hardware and software when needed
- Communicate with vendors and installers to achieve success on the current build out small or large

Jun 2003 - Dec 2004

#### I.T. ADMINISTRATOR

Mandalay Bay, Las Vegas, NV

- Administer new policies, procedures, and forecast future needs
- Answer various computer related calls, set appointments, and arrive for service or repair
- Communicate with the I.T. Director to quardinate recommended updates and upgrades on schedule
- Learn new systems quickly and troubleshoot them efficiently

## References

References available upon request